<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<channel>
  <title>[ wide / open \ space ]</title>
  <description>A place for thoughts on my first try at life on earth.</description>
  <link>https://wideopen.space/</link>
  <atom:link href="https://wideopen.space/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <lastBuildDate>Mon, 5 May 2025 10:38:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
  <language>en-us</language>

      <item>
    <title>Bad Options All Round</title>
    <link>https://wideopen.space/#article-bad-options-all-round</link>
    <guid>https://wideopen.space/#article-bad-options-all-round</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 5 May 2025 10:38:00 +0200</pubDate>
    <description><![CDATA[
      <p>I want to talk a bit about the strange position we find ourselves in—trying to make better choices but faced with bad options on either side. I’ve spent the last few years wallowing in the apathy I feel towards the businesses whose services and products I need. Lately that apathy has simmered into a thickened rage as I feel evermore trapped between startups and institutions.</p>
    ]]></description>
  </item>

    <item>
    <title>Just me and the lads and $1 bajillion in funding</title>
    <link>https://wideopen.space/#arena-gallery-component</link>
    <guid>https://wideopen.space/#arena-gallery-component</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 10:24:00 +0200</pubDate>
    <description><![CDATA[
      <p>I’ve been a user and supporter of Are.na for years. I use it to store links, references, or images, and to explore the things that others choose to store in their channels. It also works as a janky CMS—one can drop content into a channel and then pull that content in elsewhere, like I’ve done here. Some Javascript (thanks Claude) and away we go.</p>
      <p>I connected a channel I started as a repository for press photos pulled from Techcrunch, a tech news website that I’m convinced future civilisations will look back on as a timeline of our demise. These 30+ images I’ve collected as of today, 9 April, 2025, represent the corresponding number of Techcrunch articles on funding rounds of various startups since 1 January. Notice any patterns?</p>
    ]]></description>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>On Being A Conscious Consumer</title>
    <link>https://wideopen.space/#article-on-being-a-better-consumer</link>
    <guid>https://wideopen.space/#article-on-being-a-better-consumer</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2025 11:24:00 +0200</pubDate>
    <description><![CDATA[
      <p>Lately I've been trying to wriggle free of the tendrils of US hegemony, and let me tell you, this has not being going well. While I consider myself a conscious consumer I am also not willing to make the massive sacrifices that would keep my values intact.</p>
      <p>I cycle everywhere but still fly home 3 times a year to see family at a cost of ~5t of CO2 per trip. I choose hotels over AirBnB, but still buy monthly staples (cat food, cat litter, detergent) via Amazon. I eat less meat and buy seasonal vegetables, yet devour digital content served up by harmful data centres.</p>
    ]]></description>
  </item>
  
  <item>
    <title>On Running</title>
    <link>https://wideopen.space/#article-on-running</link>
    <guid>https://wideopen.space/#article-on-running</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 11:08:00 +0200</pubDate>
    <description><![CDATA[
      <p>I think I've been running for almost 13 years now. In fact, I've just confirmed this on my Nike Run Club app.</p>
      <p>What started as a counterweight to my chain smoking and binge drinking has turned into something so much more. As I look towards what I want from running in the future, I felt like I needed to take a few minutes to get my thoughts straight.</p>
    ]]></description>
  </item>
  
  <item>
    <title>HTML Energy is chill</title>
    <link>https://wideopen.space/#post-htmlenergy</link>
    <guid>https://wideopen.space/#post-htmlenergy</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 20 Mar 2021 07:44:00 +0100</pubDate>
    <description><![CDATA[
      <p>I haven't spent time on WOS in a while but I recently stubmled onto the wonderful HTML Energy podcast and I've been inspired to keep going. I love that there are so many people out there doing the same kinda thing for so many different reasons.</p>
    ]]></description>
  </item>
  
  <item>
    <title>PC Build</title>
    <link>https://wideopen.space/#post-pcbuild</link>
    <guid>https://wideopen.space/#post-pcbuild</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2020 18:58:00 +0200</pubDate>
    <description><![CDATA[
      <p>I haven't built a PC in 14 years. Here's my first attempt using scavenged parts from eBay-Kleinanzeigen. Unfortunately the RAM I purchased was not compatible with my mainboard but I'll be able to fix that soon.</p>
    ]]></description>
  </item>

</channel>
</rss>